Polish American Historical Association records 1932-2005 CPAA 05-11
Connecticut Polish American Archives, Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University, New Britain
- Series IV: Correspondence
  - PAHA Miscellaneous correspondence, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PAHA Miscellaneous correspondence, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PAHA Miscellaneous correspondence, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PAHA correspondence with the American Historical Association, 1998-2008 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PAHA Ohio chapter - correspondence and clippings compiled by Sister Clarent Marie, the Chapter President, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 16A)
  - PAHA California chapter correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - PAHA California chapter correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - PAHA California chapter meeting minutes, 1989-1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - PAHA web site development correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - PAHA correspondence with the Polish Genealogical Society, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - PAHA Treasurer correspondence, January-April, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PAHA receipts and related correspondence, January-May, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - PAHA Treasurer correspondence, January-April, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PAHA Treasurer correspondence, April-May, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PAHA Treasurer correspondence, June-July 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PAHA disbursements and related correspondence, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PAHA deposits and related correspondence, pt.1, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - PAHA deposits and related correspondence, pt.2, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PAHA deposits and related correspondence, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - PAHA Treasurer correspondence, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - PAHA disbursements and related correspondence, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - PAHA deposits and related correspondence, pt.1, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - PAHA deposits and related correspondence, pt.2, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - PAHA correspondence, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - PAHA disbursement and related correspondence, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Series III: General
  - PAHA archives transfer from St. Mary's College to the Polish Museum of America in Chicago, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - PAHA office and archives transfer to the Central Connecticut State University, related correspondence, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 1A)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, January, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, August, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, October, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, March, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, october 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, March 2001 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, October 2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, March 2003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - PAHA Newsletter material, October 2003 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - PAHA Executive Secretary report, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - PAHA correspondence related to Ohio University Press book publication, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - PAHA Polish memoirs project, 1995, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - PAHA Polish American Studies orders, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - PAHA Editorial board for Polish American Studies, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - PAHA cooperation agreement with the Polish Highlander Alliance of America, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - PAHA clippings, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - PAHA clippings, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - PAHA clippings, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - PAHA clippings, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PAHA clippings, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - PAHA clippings, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PAHA clippings, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PAHA clippings, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PAHA clippings, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - PAHA clippings, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - PAHA clippings, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PAHA clippings, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PAHA clippings, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - PAHA clippings, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - PAHA clippings, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - PAHA clippings, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - PAHA clippings, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - PAHA clippings, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - PAHA clippings, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - PAHA clippings, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - PAHA clippings, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - PAHA clippings, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - PAHA clippings, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - PAHA clippings, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - PAHA clippings, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - PAHA clippings, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - PAHA clippings, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - PAHA clippings, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - PAHA clippings, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - PAHA clippings, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - PAHA clippings, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - PAHA clippings, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - PAHA clippings, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - PAHA clippings, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - PAHA miscellaneous articles, undates (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - PAHA grant proposal to the National Endowment for Humanities, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - PAHA Kruszka translation project, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - PAHA Silesian Profiles project, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - PAHA correspondence related to publication and distribution of "Ethnic identity and assimilation", 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - PAHA Grant proposal to The Sloan Foundation, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - PAHA Grant proposal to the Illinois Humanities Council, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - PAHA agreement with the Instytut Badan Polonijnych in Poland related to article translation, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - PAHA pamphlet publication: An introduction to Polish-American Studies: a selected English bibliography, by Joseph Hapak, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - PAHA Stanley Pachon bequest, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - PAHA Stanley Anthony Kulczycki bequest, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - PAHA correspondence with Helen Stankiewicz Zand, related to publication of "Polish folkways in America", 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - PAHA Helen Stankiewicz Zand's manuscript with annotations, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - PAHA correspondence and clippings related to Polish-Jewish relations compiled by Rev. L. Chrobot, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - PAHA Questionnaire - The contribution of Polish Catholics to the church in the US, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - PAHA Questionnaire - The contribution of women's religious congregations communities to the Catholic church in America, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - PAHA Questionnaire on the contribution of Polish men's religious communities to the Catholic church in America, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - PAHA Questionnaire for Polish parishes in the US, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - "Progressives, socialists and the Milwaukee Poles" by Donald Pienkos, [1975?] (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - PAHA - clippings on Polish related issues, 1970's (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - 900th Anniversary of martyrdom of St. Stanislaus - clippings, programs, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Polish-American Communist Party - "Jak mozna wyzwolic Polske?", [1940?] (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - PAHA - Audio tapes from PAHA Board Meetings, 1974-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)